(Leonard:)So are you really not
gonna do this movie?
(Penny:)Well, I don't think it's the kind
of part that's good for my career.
(Leonard:)But don't a lot of famous actors
get their start doing bad movies?
(Penny:)Okay, I don't think Meryl Streep
ever had to say,
"Must keep gorilla hands
from killing again!"
(Raj:)If she did, it would be amazing.
That woman can do no wrong.
(Leonard:)I don't know anything
about show business,
(Leonard:)so if you think it's reasonable
to turn down paid work
and just bum through
your savings,
(Leonard:)I'm sure you know what
you're doing.
(Amy:)I think we're gonna go.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Sheldon:)We were making fun of
failed careers.
(Sheldon:)We didn't get to tap
the juicy vein that is Howard's.
(Howard:)Hey, I work
at the same university you do.
(Sheldon:)Yes, and Hawkeye's in
the Avengers,
(Sheldon:)but no one ever says,
"Help, Hawkeye!"